Guide to the Diego Cortez No Wave Collection, circa 1972-1981.
Cortez, Diego No Wave Collection,
- Posters and flyers
  - China, CBGB, 1977; Punk concert poster. Xerox. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Former members of Mars.
  - Dead Boys Fan Club, 1977; Punk poster. Xerox. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Mumps, CBGB, 1977; Punk concert poster. Xerox. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - The Diodes, CBGB, 1977; Punk poster. Xerox. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Student Teachers (w/ Bill Arning), CBGB, 1977; Punk poster. Xerox. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 24 Hours of Terror, CBGB, 1977; Punk concert poster. Xerox. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Mumps, CBGB, 1977; Punk concert poster. Xerox. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - The Looters, 1977; Punk concert poster. Xerox. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Mitchell, Eric
    Crutchfield, Robin
    Kramer, Steven
  - Flyer with a note from Herman Badillo, 1977-09 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Pasted on to a poster from Max's
  - Optica, un centre au service de l'art contemporain, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    For a screening of videos by Diego Cortez
    Montreal, Canada
  - Art D'aujourd'hui - Kunst Van Heden, 1975-05-23-1975-07-13 (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Brussels, Belgium
  - Never Mind the Bollocks, Here's the Sex Pistols, 1977-10 (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Sex Pistols poster (color, large format)
  - Never Mind the Bollocks, Here's the Sex Pistols, 1977-10 (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Sex Pistols poster (B/W, small format)
  - In Person!, 1979; Sex, John; Hand-made artists' poster. Silkscreen on paper. (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Annual Group Erotic and Pornographic Art Exhibition (Club 57), 1979; Sex, John; Hand-made artists' poster. Silkscreen on paper, pink spray paint. (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Announcement Cards
    - MoMA exhibition "Eight Contemporary Artists", 1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      DC worked for Acconci and set up his installation; this is when DC met Boetti and was invited to stay at his Rome home the following summer,1975, where Boetti introduced DC to his protege, Francesco Clemente
      Marden, Brice
      Acconci, Vito
      Boetti, Alighieri
      Rockburne, Dorothea
      Buren, Daniel
    - DC performance/film screening at Anthology Film Archives, 1975-04; Cortez, Diego; Offset on card stock. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Performance/video event at Kvindeudstillingen, Charlottenborg, 1975-12; Abramovic, Marina; Printers ink on card stock. (Box 1, Folder 24)
      Photo of MA by Ulla Poye. Card hand cut by DC and handwritten notes by DC are on verso.
      Copenhagen, Denmark
    - DC solo exhibition at Arte Fiera Bologna, Galleria Trisorio, 1976; Printers ink on card stock. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Robert Gordon album announcement card (w/ Link Wray), 1977; Offset photo card. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - DC performance/film screening at Artists Space, 1976-04; Cortez, Diego (Box 1, Folder 25)
      Evening included performance/lecture 'Hospital Colors' (1975) and screening of two films 'Like A Job' (1974) and 'Vienna, City of Song' (1976). Offset on card stock.
    - S/RS Network show featuring Liza Bear and Keith Sonnier at the Kitchen, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Recordings and artwork
  - Recording
    - POLICEBAND - Stereo/Mono, 1979; Policeband, Boris (Box 1, Folder 26)
      45 RPM EP record.
      Blair, Dike
      Vacuum Records
  - Artwork by Cortez
  - MoMA Guard, 1975-01-27; Cortez, Diego; Two panel work: MoMA letterhead, large type, red ball point pen; Black/white xerox of above. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Exhibited: "Xerox and Blood", Whitney Museum Art Resources Center, Spring 1975; "40-The Anniversary Exhibition", Hal Bromm Gallery, NYC, 2015-16.
  - Seven collage works, 1976; Cortez, Diego; Mixed media mounted on butcher paper. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Includes "Sway Back" and "Palming".
  - Artwork by others
  - El grupo de los trece en arte de sistemas, 1972-1973; Beuys, Joseph (Box 1, Folder 27)
    CAYC Arte Argentino
  - Untitled (Prinzendorf 24-hour Aktion), 1975; Nitsch, Hermann; Animal blood on linen. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    DC was a principal actor in Nitsch's first 24-hour Aktion. Gift from Nitsch to DC following 1975 Aktion.